Well today I'm going to start directly with little
Bueno hoy voy a empezar directo con
princess who apparently has
princesita que al parecer nos ha
dedicated her Stream to us I don't know if it was today or
dedicado su Stream no sé si ha sido hoy
yesterday I think it was yesterday but
o ha sido ayer creo que fue ayer pero lo
we have it today so well little
tenemos hoy así que
princess has taken stock of
bueno princesita ha hecho un balance de
her last
su de su último
year reviewing all her controversies with
año repasando todas sus polémicas con
Fran tell me Fran pay attention that you go out into the
Fran cuenta Fran atento que sales al
ring with cua with Dallas and with a certain
ruedo con cua con Dallas y con un tal
Jaime
Jaime
Olivares by name he is surely an
Olivares por el nombre seguramente es un
[ __ ] well almost the three of them are
[__] bueno casi que los tres son
a bit stupid Why are we going to deny it
un poco tontos Para qué lo vamos a negar
no and more next to little princess so
no y más al lado de princesita así que
well let's listen to her to see what
bueno vamos a escucharla a ver qué nos
this illustrious eminence
tiene que decir esta ilustre eminencia
of
de
Twitch has to tell us What madness man I really didn't know
Twitch Qué locura tío de verdad no sabía
that daa for so much really I
que daa para para tanto de verdad me
'm finding out things that I didn't know
estoy enterando de cosas que yo no sabía
about myself but how many videos is it that I keep
de de mí pero cuántos vídeos es que sigo
downloading saa look I keep downloading and there are still
bajando saa es que Mirad sigo bajando y
more videos from the other day
sigue habiendo más vídeos del otro día
literally 9 days ago and what's
literalmente hace 9 días y qué
going on well these you see these are the ones that
pasa bueno estos ves estos son los que
I upload but what a barbarity man
subo yo pero qué barbaridad tío pues es
well no what is this man if it's I don't
bueno no qué es esto tío si es que no lo
understand but I get into  in so many
entiendo pero yo me meto en tantos
messes proud to
jaleos orgullosa
deitar men no but I
deitar hombres no pero yo
that Valentina made a video proud
que Valentina le hizo un vídeo orgullosa
to parasitize men s I am s I am yes I am little
de parasitar hombres s soy s soy si soy
princess proud to parasitize
princesita orgullosa de parasitar
men the streamer who sees men
hombres la streamer que ve a los hombres
as ATMs [ __ ]
como cajeros automáticos [__]
hot But what is this dude really
buenísimo Pero qué es esto tío de verdad
noo Well
noo Bueno
t why put me here more than 18 but people
t por me pon aquí más 18 pero la gente
really have ok she is gorgeous [ __ ]
verdad teno valena está guapísima [__]
I uploaded this tweet what a basz No how
yo sub este tweet menuda basz No qué
based eh there I came out [ __ ] I
basada eh ahí he salido yo [__] Yo
uploaded this tweet Ah there I am d and
subí este twet Ah que ahí estoy yo d y
my damn Wi very open drugs ap Ah
mi condenados Wi micho abiert drog ap Ah
because it's me giving some exclusive what a
porque soy yo dando alguna exclusiva
basz No how
menuda basz No qué
based I didn't know I had uploaded this
basada no sabía que había subido este
tweet how based really this streamer
twit qué basada pasadísimo esta streamer
tells me that I have it small but but it
me dice que la tengo pequeña pero pero
is this outrage chat what is this
es esta barbaridad chat qu es esta
outrage this streamer tells me that I have it
barbaridad este streamer me dice que la
small it is
tengo pequeña es
that he is my father elor shows his support for
que es mi padre elor muestra su apoyo a
Fran United for united for the same
Fran Unidos por unidos por un mismo
destiny Javi please can you
destino Javi por favor nos puedes
explain to us at twick Why are you wearing
explicar a los de twick Por qué llevas
that Pink hat [ __ ] dude  I'm going to take it
ese sombrero Rosa [__] tío me lo voy a
off, wow, what are you giving me with
quitar vaya la que me estáis dando con
the filter, man, I put it on because,
el filtro tío me lo he puesto porque
well, I don't know, super random, I just
pues no lo sé super Random acabo de
saw it here, I pressed the button and I
verlo aquí le he dado al botón y me he
put on the hat, man. Well, now you
puesto el sombrero tío Pues ahora me
're giving me a little courage, huh. I'm going
estáis dando un poco de coraje eh Me voy
to put on a hat for each extract
a poner un sombrero por cada extracto
today, go to hell, super
hoy a tomar por culo super loco ahora
crazy now I'm going to look to see if there's a crown, I
locura tío qué barbaridad Qué locura qué
really think it's mine because a father hat, no, no, no, not to be your father, no misogyny, yes, how
verdad pensadlo O sea he tenido m vida
good, how good, let's all be misogynists, all of us ...  there are
el millor con Fran cuesto con Javi
four cats
aquí porque es que en K hay cuatro gatos
dude and the chat the chat of the
tío y el chat el chat de el chat
main chat has to go here in the
principal tiene que ir aquí en la
corner dude it's that in Kia there are four
esquina tío es que en Kia hay cuatro
cats with me What move did he have I mean
gatos conmigo Qué movida tuvo o sea
with me really a little bit of bit on
conmigo realmente un poquito de bito en
Twitter flirting like that no but
Twitter tonteo de esos no pero eso verá
you'll see that I don't know I don't care I wouldn't
tú no me yo a mí no me importa a mí no
mind
me importaría
inviting Princessita and Jan here to chat
invitar a aquí a charlar a Princesita y
not as a King eh I mean it's not like we're
Jan no de Rey eh o sea en plan no es que
going to be friends obviously but
vayamos a ser amigos evidentemente pero
no maybe you remind me and
no a lo mejor me lo recordáis y de
suddenly I get angry but it doesn't remember that he
repente me enfado pero no me suena que
said something to me like super beast like that he
me haya dicho algo en plan super bestia
hurt me You know I think
en plan que me haya dlido Sabes Me suena
we had a fight because she was
que tuvimos pique porque ella era
short
pisita
and then she
y y luego
joined the hate because it was fashionable but it doesn't
se apuntó al hate por moda pero no me
remember me like insulting each other like I don't
suena de insultarnos en plan no me
remember eh maybe yes eh It's that I
acuerdo eh que a lo mejor sí eh Es que
really forget I mean I do so many
se me olvida de verdad O sea hago tantas
things and so many interactions a day that
cosas y tantas interacciones al día que
many times I don't even remember who I
muchas veces no me acuerdo ni con quién
've
me he
fought with Kick the Twitch competition
peleado Kick la competencia de Twitch
Kick is dead imo Eh it doesn't work
Kick está muert imo Eh no tira
Eh it doesn't work Eh it doesn't
Eh no tira Eh no
work you know what happens I have very little  I
tira sabes qué pasa que tengo muy poca O
mean I don't give a damn about messing with people I
sea me la pela meterme con la gente O
mean if I see it justified if you
sea si lo veo justificado del palo si
're an idiot And you say something like that then I'll mess
eres [__] Y dices una sul pues me
with you like I'll answer you no like
meto contigo en plan te respondo no en
all men no no it's that kit
plan todos hombres no no es que de kit
dude This was a tesa thing But the thing is that I
tío Esto fue cosa de tesa Pero es que yo
think that in the end I'm going to
creo que lo de kiik al final lo voy a
remove the kiik man I think that in the end I'm
quitar tío Yo creo que lo de ki al final
going to remove it literally I don't even know
lo voy a quitar literalmente no sé ni
how much I get from kik I mean at the moment they
cuánto cobro de kik o sea en el momento
make the deposit I won't even
en que me hagan el ingreso ni me doy
realize that's how it has to be deposit it will be
cuenta así tiene que ser ingreso serán
20 or 15 or something like that I don't even I don't
20 lo o 15 o algo de eso ni ni ni los
see them ever I don't even know what day
veo nunca no sé ni qué día
it will be misandry it won't be misogyny they
será misandria no será misoginia ellos
did m no Sky also have a thing with Sky
hací m no Sky también ten movida con Sky
I've had a thing with ibai to a certain
he tenido movida con ibai hasta cierto
point let's see but with sk she liked her
punto a ver pero con sk le gustaba Ella
not but it's that I've had a thing with
no pero es que tenida movida con todo el
everyone not with Lali with the girlfriend from this it
mundo no con Lali con la novia del este
's that they are all so [ __ ] only
es que son todos tan subnormales solo
with one girl well and the girl
con una chica bueno y la chica también
was also she just called me [ __ ] you and I
era me acaba de llamar subnormal tú y yo
here saying no I princess
aquí diciendo no yo princesita la
would invite her no  has never insulted me, I'm
invitaría no me ha insultado nunca
sure he has insulted me and I don't
seguro que si me ha insultado y no me
remember. I mean, imagine, but now I'm
acuerdo O sea imagínate pera ahora
also telling you, base it on everything, I mean, I have
también te digo basad ima en todo o sea
n't had any in which he has
no he tenido ninguna en la que me haya
seen me and says anything, very based, I mean, I think that when
visto y diga nada basadisimo o sea yo
Cristinini was most based, I was going to call her, why would I
cristinini le iba a llamar por qué le
call her Cristinini, little princess. I think that when she was most
iba a decir cristinini princesita yo
based, little princess, base it
creo que cuando más basada estuvo
on everything, eh, I think
princesita basad sima en todo eh yo creo
that when she was most empty
que cuando más vazada estuvo
was when she said that
fue cuando dijo que con el simple hecho
simply by being in Andorra I learned Catalan. I mean, you are there in Andorra and little by little you acquire Catalan, this is as if in 2020 you went out on the street and you sat down, you didn't sit on
la calle y te sentabas no te sentabas en
the doorstep of your
la puerta de de tu
block and you sucked on it from time to time, the
bloque y chupabas la de vez en cuando la
railing of the stairs, you
La barandilla de las escaleras tú te
stayed there and little by little you
quedabas allí y poco a poco ibas
acquired covid. Well, in Andorra the
adquiriendo covid Pues en andorra te
same thing happens but with Catalan, let's see
pasa lo mismo pero con el Catalán a ver
if you are a YouTuber and you are locked up all the time
si eres youtuber y estás todo el tiempo
and such, well, you know. Open the
encerrado y tal pues tú sabes Abre la
window from time to time  you go out the
ventana de vez en cuando sales a la
window and get some Catalan that
ventana y pillas un poco de Catalán que
reaches you okay So it reaches you I have not
te llegue vale Así que te llegue no he
been based host what a mistake nothing
estado basada [__] menudo error nada
nothing passed with all I mean all
nada pasada con todos o sea todos
misogynists to take by ass I mean what do they
misóginos a tomar por culo O sea qué
all have in common chat and the truth is
tienen todos en común chat y la verdad
that after all the funas it's like I'm
que después de todas las funas es como
surprised they don't have But what the
que me sorprende el no tener Pero qué
[ __ ] does misogyny have to do with it Or rather
[__] tiene que ver la misoginia O sea la
criticism Or rather the fight with me if I
crítica O sea la bronca conmigo si no
remember correctly it was because he posted a tweet
recuerdo mal era porque puso un tweet
taking the
sacando un click de contexto lo del
Dallas and Star yuki thing out of context And I told him let's see
Dallas y Star yuki Y yo le dije a ver
that I get along with Star yuki but
que yo me llevo con Star yuki pero que
Yi is exactly boom Pam no and I explained it to him
Yi tal cual pum Pam no y se lo expliqué
and he blocked me but apart from that well I
y me bloqueó pero aparte de eso bueno Me
imagine I take it for granted having
imagino yo doy por hecho ya habiéndola
heard it that he has surely insulted me
escuchado que me habrá insultado
in some Stream I feel sorry
seguramente en algún Stream yo lo siento
for anug But I still bet on the
por anug Pero sigo apostando por la
couple crybaby princess 51 do you know where I
pareja princesita llorón 51 sabéis dónde
saw anug the other
vi anug el otro
day I said it on today's news
día lo dije en el noticiero de hoy puede
maybe it was outside of today yes I didn't say anything
ser que fuera de hoy sí no lo dije nada
because we haven't commented on this either
porque tampoco hemos comentado esto
but the other day Jorge Javier Vquez
pero el otro día Jorge Javier váquez le
made a  interview with
hizo una entrevista a
sz Pedro Snchez The president of
sz Pedro Sánchez El presidente de de
our government
nuestro gobierno
no
no
and presented a book and then Jorge
y presentaba un libro y entonces Jorge
Javier presented the
Javier lo presentaba el
event which by the way this
evento que por cierto esto
was Javi you are very handsome with the
estuvo Javi estás muy guapo con el
teleno hat thank goodness Thank goodness that
sombrero teleno menos mal Menos mal que
by the way this I mean this event I
por cierto esto O sea este evento se
think was paid for and organized and all
creo que se pagó y se organizó y todo
this of the I mean the video I don't know where it was
esto de la O sea el vídeo yo no sé dónde
broadcast if it was broadcast on the
se retransmitió si se retransmitió por
internet or where but the video I mean it
internet o por dónde pero el vídeo o sea
's from the State the government cannot
es de del Estado del gobierno no puede
finance with public money an act that
financiar con dinero público un acto que
is personal of your book But anyway
que es personal de tu libro Pero bueno
La Movida let's see if I can find the clip look look look
La Movida a ver si encuentro el clip
who's coming out here
Mira mira mira mira quién sale por aquí
was all happy to see their idol
era todo contento de ver a su ídolo
look but look at you in a country where
mira pero fíjate tú que en un país que
we have been 40 years with a
hemos estado 40 años con una
dictatorship that was hot they said there you
dictadura que hacía calor decían ahí lo
have it look heat there Oh damn can't you see it
tenéis mir calor ahí Ay [__] no lo veis
with me there's the guy there's the guy
conmigo ahí está el tío ahí está el tío
there but but but like me when I'm
ahí pero pero pero como yo cuando estoy
watching the cabar cats at Disneyland
viendo las cabar gatas de Disneylandia
eh look and well there were some leaders
eh mira y bueno hubo algunos dirigentes
super happy like I find
está super contento como yo encuentro
Chinese watching Paula chb barra
chino viendo a Paula chb barría
and the promo from the  official account of the is
y la promo desde la cuenta oficial de la
that clear It's that look government of
es que claro Es que mira gobierno de
Spain Look at the seal you see it from the
España Mira el sello lo ves des el
popular party that I little less than I I
partido popular que me poco menos que me
mean you can't
O sea no puedes
eh You can't or you shouldn't let's see power
eh No puedes o no deberías a ver poder
can do it has done it but you shouldn't
puede hacerlo la ha hecho pero no
eh You
eh No
shouldn't finance that with
deberías financiar eso con dinero
public money it's not the presentation of your
público no es la presentación de tu
book that what I was telling you guys
libro que lo queos iba diciendo chavales
Let's see what is the word that is used
A ver cuál es la palabra que se utiliza
to define Anne or rather for
al Anne para definir o sea para los
men hatred or rather men or women I
hombres el odio o sea hombres o mujeres
don't understand no misogyny the word I
no entiendo no misoginia la palabra
understand that it can also be used
entiendo que también se puede utilizar
for women no Or for women it doesn't apply I
para mujeres no O para mujeres no aplica
mean misogyny hatred towards the
o sea misoginia odio hacia el género
feminine gender the word towards the hatred
femenino la palabra hacia el el odio
towards the masculine gender is misandre
hacia el género masculino es misandre
misandry was the
misandria era la
word or I've smoked a huge joint
palabra o me he fumado un porro enorme
I'm making a fool of myself with a pink hat
estoy haciendo el ridículo con un gorro
well she she would have Miss andria
pues ella ella sí tendría Miss andria
no I mean little
no O sea
princess yes she would have Miss
princesita sí tendría Miss
Andrea of course I mean she Calls
Andrea claro O sea ella Llama misogino a
everyone who argues with her a misogynist and it's
todo el que al que discute con ella y es
like well let's
como bueno a
see where the
ver dónde está la
misogyny is I mean it's that on many
misoginia o sea es que en muchas
occasions discussing things that have nothing to
ocasiones discutiendo cosas que ni
do with with gender
tienen que ver con con con el género
feminine nor masculine nor with them being
femenino ni masculino ni con que sean
women
mujer
discussions with Sky I don't know what
discusiones con Sky No sé lo que le
happened to her but well The misogyny thing is
pasó pero bueno La Movida misoginia es
that you treat women badly and in a
que tú trates mal a las mujeres y de
derogatory way because they are
forma despectiva por el hecho de ser
women because you hate
mujeres porque tienes odio contra las
women but that you but that you argue
mujeres pero que tú pero que tú discutas
with a [ __ ] that I tell you
con una petarda que te digo
no but she would be misandrist no
no pero ella sí sería misándrica no
because she simply
porque es que ella simplemente tiene
hates men
odio hacia los hombres
and claims things like that she likes to
y Afirma cosas como que que le gusta
profit from men and that she sees them
lucrarse de los hombres y que los ve
as an ATM according to that
como un cajero automático según ese
headline of the video no Of course She would be
titular del vídeo no Claro Ella sí sería
misandrist what she Calls all the
misándrica lo que ella Llama a todos los
all the men with whom she fights
a todos los hombres con los que se pelea
she is against men afraid to
ella sí lo es contra los hombres miedo a
speak or I mean it's like after
hablar o sea es como que después de
all the insults all the videos I still don't give a damn
todos los insultos todos los vídeos aún
or I mean like I can spend a
así me la pela o sea tipo puedo pasar un
bad day because of the hate or whatever but the
día mal por el hate o lo que sea pero al
next day it's like I forget everyone
día siguiente es como se me olvida todos
in common that they pay taxes tax havens I
en común que tributan paraísos Fiscales
laugh my dick Tas or that every
me parto la [__] Tas oa que cada
altercation you have with a person the
altercado que tengas con una persona la
only answer is that that person is
única respuesta es que esa persona es
misogynistic No no In fact no In fact I have a
misoga No no De hecho no De hecho tengo
thing  because he just said that everyone
movida porque acaba de decir que todos
pays taxes in tax havens let's see what
tributa en paraísos Fiscales a ver ha
Agustn 51 said he's in Andorra
dicho Agustín 51 que está en andorra
utbh I don't know if he got to Andorra or
utbh no sé si se llegó ahí a andorra o
not I spoke to him recently and I think
no Yo hablé hae poco con él y creo que
the
el
phone number was the same I don't know if you
teléfono era el mismo que no sé si
change phones if you change countries I
cambias de teléfono si cambias de país
don't know if you change the prefix or if you already
No sé si cambias el prefijo o si ya lo
have it from before he still has it I don't know the truth let's
tienes de antes sigue No lo sé la verdad
see Agustn he's in Andorra utbh I do
e a ver Agustín que está en andorra utbh
n't know if he's in Andorra but he's leaving
que no sé si está en andorra pero se va
and [ __ ] off this [ __ ] new application is giving me
e vaya por culo me está dando la [__]
eh the Twitter of
aplicación esta nueva eh el Twitter de
[Music]
[Música]
Instagram skin is not in Andorra no
Instagram skin no está en andorra no
skin he's going to be in Andorra if not
skin que va a estar en andorra si no lo
even Peter sees it
ve ni Peter
and Javi Oliveira is tremendously handsome
e Y Javi oliveira es tremendamente guapo
and attractive
y atractivo
and he doesn't look like he's 38
y no parece que tenga 38
years old but he doesn't pay taxes in Andorra he pays taxes
años pero no tributa en andorra tributa
in
en
Andalusia tax haven Andalusia but the thing is that
Andalucía paraíso fiscal Andalucía pero
in any case Andorra is not a
es que de todas manera andorra no es un
tax haven I go way beyond that and they don't
paraíso fiscal pondo mucho más allá y no
know what to answer And then what
saben qué contestar Y entonces lo que
they answer is Haha eh fat girl Haha [ __ ] Haha
contestan es Jaja eh gorda Jaja [__]
That's it  what those are your
Jaja Eso es lo que eso son sus
answers that's my of men yes
respuestas eso es mi de hombres sí
exactly no but it's true dude I
exacto no pero es que es verdad tío O
mean bada in everything dude I mean I
sea que badía en todo tío o sea te lo
promise you Eh I see myself again and I say go on
prometo Eh me vuelvo a ver y digo va
I'm totally crazy about absolutely everything how
estoy vadima en absolutamente todo qué
crazy are all instel misogynists or
barbaridad son todos instel misóginos o
third world or all three at the same time
trer mistas o las tres cosas a la vez
But why do you always have to be
Pero por qué siempre tenéis que estar
talking about Ricky I really I mean
hablando de Ricky yo de verdad O sea
Lu I mean they are
Lu O sea que son
third world and that everyone when they
tercermundistas y que todos cuando
argue with her they say Haha [ __ ] That's
discuten con ella le dicen Jaja [__] Eso
not true only Fran does that it's just
no es verdad eso solo lo hace Fran es
that only Fran has done I have
solo eso solo lo ha hecho Fran Yo no le
never told her anything like that but I think
he dicho Nunca nada de eso pero yo creo
the most times I've said to her has been a
que lo más vez que le he dicho ha sido
jerk today but that I don't I don't
petarda hoy pero que que yo no no
remember having a really strong fight with
recuerdo haberme peleado muy fuerte con
this girl I mean We laughed and we
esta chica o sea Nos reímos y nos lo
took it as a joke no content third
tomamos a coña no contenido tercer
world eh third world eh you
mundista eh tercer mundista eh se
allow yourself to be classist careful
permite ser clasista cuidado
eh The little princess
eh La princesita
eh I see myself again and I say go on I'm totally
eh me vuelvo a ver y digo va estoy
crazy about absolutely everything how
basima en absolutamente todo qué
crazy are all instel misogynists  or
barbaridad son todos instel misóginos o
third world or all three at the
tercermundistas o las tres cosas a la
same time But why do you always have to be
vez Pero por qué siempre tenéis que
talking about Rick, really? I
estar hablando de Rick yo de verdad O
mean, then
sea luego
elens that I'm obsessed with it's my chat
elens que estoy obsesion con es mi chat
chat obsessed,
chat obsesionados
my best
mi mejor de
taste If we talk about it in passing, already for a
gusto Si lo comentamos de paso yao el
while, even in person and
rato hasta en persona y
tell him
decirle
this, I think we put it today, not in the
esto creo que lo pusimos hoy no en el
news, no luare, that says that if he
noti no luare que dice que si se
meets Rick one day he's going to call him "
encuentra Rick un día le va a decir
carapolla" in a way. No, if I run into him in
carapolla de forma No si me lo cruzar en
person, it would be best to say "carapolla"
persona lo mejor le diría e carapolla
now I'm not going to do it because he'll
ahora no lo voy a hacer porque
probably record if I pass him the
probablemente vaya grabando si le pas el
clip "carapolla" insult
clip carapolla insulto
chat then you say you have things "carapolla"
chat luego dices que tien movidas
insult chat "carapolla" is it an
carapolla insulto chat carapolla es
insult or is it a compliment It depends, depends on
insulto o es un piropo Depende depende
the dick it is, no chat chat chat "
la [__] que sea no chat chat chat
carapolla" is an insult
carapolla es
Let's see, it's an adjective, it's not an
insulto A ver es un adjetivo no es un
adjective, no, it shouldn't be an
adjetivo no no tendría por qué ser un
insult, I don't know, there's a
insulto no sé hay
misogynist in the middle of winter and in short sleeves,
misógino pleno invierno y en manga corta
that one, let's see, well, she's in short sleeves and let's
esa a ver bueno está en manga corta y a
see, in short sleeves, they're not fastened, they're not
ver en manga corta no están sujetado no
fastened. Don't be a
están sujetado No seas
misogynist, thanks, the situation is in a
misógino graci la situación está en
bra  I understand No I was
sujetador entiendo No yo lo estaba
watching it I mean before there was a sweatshirt and Aha there
viendo digo antes estaba sudadera y Aha
's a bra but I imagine that I
está sujetador pero me imagino que me
imagine that she did it to get
imagino que lo ha hecho para ponerse
comfortable because she's doing a
cómoda porque está haciendo una
craft not with some stickers
manualidad no con unas pegatinas
noada no but I go with I go with people
noada no pero voy con voy con gente de
who wouldn't do anything to me you know if you see
que no me haría nada sabes si ves a
Riquita in person you'll
riquita en persona te cabas encima
probably not
probablemente no
eh I mean probably I wouldn't tell her
eh o sea probablemente no le diría
because I'm
porque soy
polite The girl is very polite eh she is
educada Es muy educada la muchacha eh es
super polite the girl would say
super educada la muchacha le diría
Good morning carapolla Good morning
Buenos días carapolla Buenos días
carapolla a very
carapolla una chica muy
polite girl But Javi take it away That talks about
educada Pero Javi quita Eso habla de lo
Orlock What is this about Orlock what
de orlock Qué es lo de orlock qué ha
happened something happened
pasado ha pasado
What happened what is this about Orlock
algo Qué ha pasado qué es lo de orlock
is that I really didn't give a damn I
es que me la pelara una barbaridad yo me
started following him What's the name of
empezó a seguir el Cómo se llama el
Delox his name is Ojo the one from the simp How
delox se llama ojo el de los simp Qué
nice the guy the Orlock thread
simpático el cabrón el hilo de orlock
But what is Luar you
Pero eso qué es luar me lo has
put it to me how nice Delo is eh but it's
puesto qué simpaticón el delo eh pero es
to get information about
por informarse de
fashion princess it's to get information about
moda princesita es para informarse de la
fashion the one from the podcast this weirdo Why are the
moda el del podcast este rarete Por qué
editions in the chat man I don't
ediciones está metado el chat hombre no
know why  what do you think Why do you think Why do
sé por qué crees Por qué usted cree por
you think It could be for something Whatever it is Whatever it
qué usted cree puede ser por algo por lo
is the athlete Whatever it
que sea sea por lo que sea el atleta por
is If you are a fan of an But what
lo que sea si eres un fan de an Pero qué
Obsession do you have with an But what has an happened to you Oh
Manía tenéis con an Pero qué se ha hecho
anu anu what has he done to you Oh anu
an Ay anu anu que os ha hecho Ay el anu
what has he done to you Wait wait Wait wait Wait wait Wait wait no
que os ha
man no no no no no no this line no this line no no no no no no
no tío no no no no no no este trazo no
no
este trazo no no no no no no no